The objective is to give correct answers.
(Sheldon:)If I know them,
why shouldn't I give them?
(Howard:)Some of us might have
the correct answers too.
(Sheldon:)- Please. You don't even have a Ph.D.
- All right, that's it.
- Howard, sit down.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)- We should take a little break.
- Good idea. I need my wrist brace.
(Sheldon:)All this button pushing is aggravating
my old Nintendo injury.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
(Howard(after Raj whispers in his ear):)I agree.
(Penny:)What did he say?
(Howard:)He compared Sheldon to a disposable
feminine cleansing product...
(Howard:)...one might use on a summer's eve.
(Penny:)Yeah, and the bag it came in.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, excellent.
I wanna show you something.
Can it wait? I need to talk to you.
(Sheldon:)Just look. I've designed
the perfect uniforms for our team.
The colors are based
on Star Trek: The Original Series.
(Sheldon:)The three of you will wear support red
and I will wear command gold.